making
Moment
on the napkin
Goodbye, my friend !ạn neille!
Goodbye, your brother
Welcome back! Hello everyone!
Welcome back!
I'm so excited I am here
to make a plan for MWI-BOI!
Still no one with the best!
All right!
My name is Maid on May!
Hey!
Maid on Princess!
You can't touch yourself
Keep holdingق With the return
of Crimson Supernova Manani,
Made Alien plans to raid
the Oikido and Cafe.
However, an internal leak drags
the police into the picture
and in a rage Manani tracks
down the rat who squealed.
It is none other than Nerula,
who swore an oath of sisterhood
with a maid from the Oinky Doink.
Manami executes Nerula
in a flash of gunfire,
leading her to die in the
arms of her hopeless sister.
A week after the gunning down of an Akiba
maid, a maid who claims to be responsible,
has turned herself in to the
Akihabara police station.
The suspect is the manager of
the cafe where the victim worked,
and according to police,
she is repeating nonsense such as
the cosmos vanished from the victim.
Investigators will look into a
possible psychiatric evaluation.
I can't believe it's already been a week.
It was quite a shock when Ranko brought
back Nagomiel covered in blood, wasn't it?
I'm surprised that the made alien
people backed off so easily.
Why is that?
I don't know.
However, it seems certain that
they plan on attacking us.
We'll work on keeping watch again.
Do you think Nagomi will
be coming back soon?
I hope she's doing okay.
Hey, everyone.
If anyone asks, Nagomi's
out sick again today.
Ronko, are you okay? I'm fine.
I'm going to focus on my duties.
Now that we have you back, Miss Minami,
we swear we're with you
all the way to the end.
Yes, to the end.
To outer space and beyond.
There's less of us now, but
the ones left are ready to go.
The wussies will come around once
we smash up that hog-filled pigsty.
I wouldn't count on that.
Shit!
Ugaki, you're the one who went and let
made alien get all soft and weak, remember?
I just did what my old boss told me to do.
My predecessor changed things
around after you got locked up.
She realized money's more
important than strength.
Don't lie to me!
Hey!
The head I knew would
have never put up with
Wuv Wuv Moonbeam getting
crushed like that,
you lying slug!
Shit, that's hot!
I told you the truth, dammit!
Well, what's real to me is different
from your version of the truth.
Huh?
Please, for Pygmy, sir.
Oh, that's quite alright.
Want a Roe Hamptick time?
Come to Oinky Doink.
Looking for a Roe Hamptick time?
Come to Oinky Doink Café.
Hey there, I'm a ninja.
Come get a discount
coupon, 5 % off, good sirs.
Hey, Nagomi.
My name is not Nagomi, I'm sorry!
A humble cup of tea, my good lady, Ninnin.
I know of a maid that goes
by the name of Nagomi.
She is missing and we are
all very worried about her.
I bet this maid is
living happily somewhere.
I'm sure this Nagomi you speak of
just wasn't cut out to be a maid.
I wonder, then, why Nogomi wanted
to be a maid in the first place.
Well, if I were to guess, probably
because maids are so cute, maybe.
Then do you suppose
she's disillusioned now?
No, that's not it!
It's likely she's just
disappointed in herself.
By the way, what is it ninjas do?
Well, we throw kunai, ninja stars,
there's smoke bombs, and nunchucks.
Oh, and fling poi everywhere!
And do you find that to be fun?
It is!
Ninjas are the best!
As long as you do your ninjitsu
training and stay stealthy, it's safe.
Unlike mates who love shootouts and guns.
Really, being a ninja is so much fun!
So... fun.
Of course being a ninja isn't fun!
A ninja isn't what I really want to be!
But it's just no use anymore.
Even at the most crucial
moment, I didn't do anything.
I relied on everyone else.
That's why, Nerula,
I don't want to see someone else die, just
because I'm useless and couldn't help.
So that's why.
I can't be a maid anymore.
But that's precisely why, Nogomi,
I want you to stay a maid.
What you're saying right now,
I don't understand at all.
Maybe one day!
Anyway, as I'm but a humble ninja now,
I will make my exit in a puff of smoke.
I found Nogumi. What? Where?
Still in town, but she's
a ninja now A ninja?
That's too funny She's still an Akiba?
They'll kill her if they find out!
Why didn't you bring her back?
Because she's a ninja.
She's not a maid anymore.
What do you think we should do, Chief?
She's still employed by
the oinky-doink, isn't she?
She might come back, right?
I mean, she's a ninja!
What is that supposed to mean?
Oh hell, I don't know!
Nagomi, be the maid you are now.
I'll have the ninja rations.
Nagonin, it's your very
first lord asking for you.
What?
My lords, thank you so
much for choosing me.
I'm deeply honored.
I'm known as stealthy ninja.
Nagonin, is it really you, Nagomi?
Uh, um, were you at Oinky Doink?
You must be mistaken.
We are all fans of Narula.
The maid called Ronko at Oinky
Doink, told us where you were.
She said that you're hiding in stealth.
Here.
No, really, I'm not.
There's something we wanted to give you.
Here, my sister, Nerula.
We didn't mean to make you cry.
Sorry.
We're so sorry.
So it really is you, Nagomi?
Wait, why are you crying?
Dude, it's just I've never had
a favorite mate die before.
It's awful.
You're right.
The same for me.
I guess this is what it's
like to have a favorite die.
Nerula was my sweetheart. She was.
such a good maid, you know?
She had a good set of
standards that she adhered to.
Remember her saying to dream big.
Think, dream big, go, go.
Think, dream big, go, go, okay?
It's because of me that.
Nerula
died.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
No, please don't say that, Nogomi.
We didn't come here to
accuse you or anything.
Nerula always said nice
things about you, Nogomi.
She said you'd make a
really good maid one day.
Nogomi will change what it means
to be a maid here in Akiba.
I'm sure of it.
She said that?
Here, you should keep
this to remember her by.
Hey, you.
You're not going back to the cafe?
Even if I decided to go back,
I'd just drag everybody down.
That kid such a terrible
shame what do you think
I can do to repay Nerula
for being my sister?
I've been running that ramen joint
for years and the people love
that the taste is always the Same
but actually that's not true I
changed the flavor a lot some things
you gotta change in Order to stay
the same I don't quite understand
uh was this someone else's order?
Thanks Time again.
Some things you have to change
in order to stay the same.
Two, four, six...
There's like a lot of them!
I've got seventeen maids in all.
Let's go alert the others.
So they're coming for us now?
That's more than double our numbers.
We're done for.
I can't die.
I just got my nails redone.
And I got a fishing pole I
never had the chance to use.
All right, then.
Time to hunt us some pigs. Yeah!
No good.
We've got maids on the windows.
The swine of nowhere to run to. Perfect.
But then this is the only entrance.
Take that!
Don't mess with us!
Get back here, punk!
You're not getting away!
Can't we talk this out?
Let's put our guns down and chat!
We've got a hostage here, damn it! Shit!
You really think we'd give a
damn about some stupid hostage?
Go on!
Cover the top floors first!
Right!
We're shooting back like a
hundred for every bullet we shoot!
So that means dead.
Now, who cares, we're gonna die!
That's from outside.
It might be some Creatureland backup.
You all go take a look.
That's weird.
There's no one here.
But if they send backup,
we'll be cornered.
Stay on the lookout.
Right.
All out of your foolish
tricks, huh, pig heads?
Get out here!
Though I ain't gonna let you die easy.
I'm sorry.
They just got past the third floor.
They've got us trapped.
Yumechi, be ready.
I shall charge out on the offense.
You need to use that chance
to take out their leader.
Huh?
Are you for real?
They have too much firepower.
We don't have enough
ammunition left either.
If you go out now, you'll die.
That won't be a problem if I
can protect this cafe. Bronco.
Come on out, Peggy's!
What the?
Who the hell are you? A ninja?
That's a ninja?
Just a ninja!
Miss Minami looks like a ninja.
I am not a ninja!
I'm a maid!
This stops right now!
What? Damn it!
Bronco, I want to be a maid after all.
I'm done running.
We can talk later.
Ah, shit.
What the hell?
Time to die!
Damn it! My turn!
Punk-ass bitch, I'll fucking kill you!
I won't let you hurt anyone else!
I want to live here! In Akiba!
Look at them go! We're going too! Wait!
Take that!
You shit!
It's Monami!
Let go of me!
We can't let these pigs win!
If you die, what's gonna
happen to me an alien?
Let go of me, dammit!
Don't you run away from me!
All of you, go after them!
Go on, get her.
You've got a score to settle, right?
She's all yours, Runco.
Please take care of things here.
Okay.
Those buggers are going
to slaughter all of them.
Let's call for backup.
As long as we can get more support,
we can go back and win this damn war.
What did you just say, Yugaki?
The war's already begun.
You can cut the tough talk.
You vermin can go ahead
and squash each other.
We don't give a damn about you anymore.
We're going to be creatures from now on.
Huh?
What the hell does that mean?
Us aliens will join hands with
the creatures and live in harmony.
Consider it a merger.
We've come to an understanding
beyond the Stargate, if you will.
Manami, thanks for all you did for us.
I hope you at least die peacefully.
Oh, bitch!
Sorry, Miss Manami.
You really are so very useless.
I'm sorry.
Forget it. Just go.
Miss Manami... Beat it. Go on. Now leave.
well now little missy here to
settle the score huh I can't
forgive you for what you did
so what What you gonna do,
then?
You gonna kill me, hun? Huh?
Bet you can't, though.
You're no cafe maid, Missy.
I am a maid.
You're a stealthy ninja. I'm a maid!
A wannabe maid who's a
useless piece of shit!
Please stop, Bronco.
If we continue to let her live,
she'll just come attack us again.
No doubt you've got that right.
It's a shame, isn't it?
Nagomi, I need you to please step aside.
I'm not moving.
Think you're over there protecting me?
What a fucking insult,
ninja maid. Move it.
My bad against your gun, huh?
Pitch me a good one.
You really want to fight that badly?
An Akiba maid has got to fight.
That's not what being a maid is about.
You've got to be kidding me.
A maid would rather have a glorious
death over living in utter disgrace.
If you die, all your masters
will be sad, won't they?
Ramen changes over time
and so should Akiba maids!
What the hell does that mean, ninja freak?
Your sister must be crying down in hell.
Nerula said I should
stay just the way I am.
So there's no point in us
killing the likes of you.
Fucking wuss.
You just don't have what it
takes to fight to the death.
I will never forgive you,
but I won't kill you.
That's the kind of maid
I'm going to be now.
Enough of your shit.
Bright-eyed youthful opinion time is over!
Ah!
Live, dammit!
Stop your killing!
If you're a real maid, then feel
the lovey-dovey heart within you!
You're a stealthy ninja, ain't ya?
Why'd I have to hear that dumbass
shit from a fucking ninja, huh?
I told you I'm a maid!
Lovey-dovey heart!
You're such a big pain in the ass.
Pig hunting's over now, ninja!
Time to get back to outer space.
I'm now gonna be my own maid.
One that Nerula would be proud of.
Welcome home, Nogomi!
You're a true maid.
I'm back now.
Stinks like creatures in here.
Ugaki, I can see that
collar around your neck.
I wouldn't underestimate me if I were you.
Look at you now, all big
and mighty with your gun.
You afraid of me?
I won't let you make a
fool out of me anymore.
Careful now or you might start
sounding like a real maid.
Now get ready to become a stardust memory.
Damn, that hurts.
I never thought it would
hurt this much to live.
I see.
A job well done, Ms. Ugaki.
And so,
Manami's plan to take over Made
Alien headquarters and wage
war on the Creatureland Group
ended in absolute failure.
A faction of the Made Alien Group
that opposed the merger broke
away, and the second generation had
Yugaki once again returned to power.
However, having lost their
Warhawks,
Made Alien had no choice but to agree
to all of Creatureland's demands,
dashing Yugaki's
hopes for a merger on equal terms.
Consequently,
Creatureland swallowed
Made Alien whole in the
and the Maid alien group
effectively disappeared.
No one knows what became of Manami,
the Maid called the Crimson Supernova.
Thus, Akihabara entered an era
of Creatureland group domination.
They would have been
better off roasted whole.
Thank you for listening to this video.